Hey guys, Manav Children She Defined
Level-1 Investment Advisor, welcome to
this YouTube channel. So today
in this video we will take up orchid setup and
in the video we will talk about some of its
friend stocks, but
before that, if you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
you must subscribe to it for such daily market
and keep the notifications on so that you can
subscribe to the notifications of our videos.
We start this video here.
First of all, if we look at yesterday or
Dow Jones can be seen at 31412 and S&P 500 at 1000
and Next, a record Kunwar Pitroda can be
seen. After this, we can see crude oil at
62.04 and gold below 800.
Due to which today here in the stock
market Prithvi Singh Bisht has taken a little
down Nifty to 5300 and now Tata Motors,
Wipro, Infosys and Dr. Reddy's Labs are
continuing their profit booking in the real estate market and
in derivatives  Even now, the Egg can be seen as a net move. At
this time, if we look at the
overall market outlook, then here we will be
able to see a slight rise due to fabric features and
today we can expect some support and points of Nifty in the market. There is
an automated subscribe here
and its completion, due to
which you
can see a little police here.
After this, if we look at the Q3 results of Nasik India, then
this company has posted only one post,
which last year gave us a quarter
inch 72.60 paste, which
shows 23.01 as compared to last year. Due to this,
here on a little side, it has
subscribed to the gift to do its business in Maharashtra. The company investing in it has
shrunk by setting this car on alarm,
click on it here and this issue has given us
50% oversubscribe here. Hearty
welcome friends, I am telling you
about UltraTech Cement, so here it has increased its
unsecured or subordinated unconditional
US dollar note which  A quarter inch Harold is a
dominant leg of SP Singh in the exchange security playlist or
a tattoo is set on it which
starts the ABC playlist here
so here is your question so
this illegal solution which is a pin
text of which is running a new bank
platform here, the ride point of the
ninth class is to buy a pin here
because of this this point in the company is in this cycle
with Tamil Nadu because of this you should
subscribe here for the next
few days you will see a slight side from your
top
stomach because of this
you will see a slight decline in the meter cycle here or Delhi for the next few
days if you see this with the industry for the
next few days you will see a similar decline in this, in this
we see the
youth running Domino's Pizza started their video,
subscribe here so it was
2.5 on the first day but one thing
I am noticing is that its EP is seen
decreasing very rapidly here
and in Eureka IPL cricket this
holiday times over subscribed and if we
talk about its grey market films then do this  That
we do not get to see anyone in the market, so you will have to
pump your addition in such a way that your
chances of getting it are very less in the medium,
so you can announce your withdrawal on day three here in day life, along with this,
here
we are inverter, I have come, like this video
and every day you exam similar market
update chapter, we are ander subscribe our
Channel and maturity hotspot of power
telegram meeting links are in the
destruction of improvement and tagged s